翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Now, if we really want to impress people or be able to communicate, we should probably get our terminology straight.
我们需要学习一些术语，才能和别人很好地交流
So let's talk about some terms.
让我们谈一谈
Up top here, we have an instance variable.
最上面这个称为实例变量
This is a variable that tracks a property of a specific instance of the current class.
这是一个跟踪当前类特定实例属性的变量
So here we have weight in pounds,
这里是以磅为单位的重量
but we could, in principle, have other properties of the dog,
原则上可以是狗的其他属性
like the weight--
比如重量...
wait, we already have the weight,
等等我们已经有重量了
sorry-- the height, the favorite color,
那就比如高度，最喜欢的颜色
like job, favorite food, favorite city in Italy,
工作，最喜欢的食物，最喜欢的意大利城市
whatever it is that a dog might want to do.
不管狗想做什么
Here, we have the constructor.
这里是构造函数
And in our case, we just had one parameter that set a single instance variable.
这个例子中只有一个参数来设置实例变量
And in principle, you could do whatever you want in this constructor,
原则上在构造函数中可以做任何事
though, typically, one of the most important things is setting all the instance variables.
不过一般最重要的就是设置实例变量
But you don't have to set all of them.
也不必全部设置
You can let it stay at the default value.
可以让它们保持默认值
We won't talk about this in these videos,
视频中就不讨论这个了
but, you know, there's various fun corner cases about setting or not setting things.
有很多设置或不设置变量的小例子
But the constructor tells you how to construct an instance of the object.
构造函数会告诉你如何实例化对象
And then lastly here, we have a so-called non-static-- or also known as an instance method.
最后这里是一个非静态（实例）方法
And the basic idea here-- we notice that static is not there.
可以发现这里没有 static
And an instance method is one that is invoked by a specific instance.
实例方法由一个具体实例调用
So you can think about it this way--
可以这样想
if we have a dog named Steve, right?
假设我们有一支叫 Steve 的狗
It's in the Steve variable.
方法就在 Steve 变量中
If we tell Steve, Steve.makeNoise,
如果我们调用 Steve.makeNoise()
then Steve will use Steve's weight in pounds to decide which behavior Steve is going to do.
然后 Steve 根据体重进行相应的行为
So roughly speaking, if, when you're reading the method you could say,
粗略地说，阅读这个方法时
if my weight is less than 10, then "yipyipyip!"
如果我的体重小于10，那么发出“yip”的叫声
and so forth, then that means it's a method that is non-static.
这样就意味着它是非静态方法
And in fact, if you need to use any of my instance variables,
事实上，访问实例变量
if you have this static keyword, it'll get confused,
如果有 static 关键词很混乱
and it will say, you cannot access an instance variable from a static context.
会提示无法在静态上下文中访问实例变量
So that's the-- and we'll get a more nuanced view of that in the next little section of these videos.
后面的一个视频会更详细地介绍
So a little more terminology--
再谈谈其他的术语
when we did our dog launching, we had a pretty simple dog launching procedure.
来看看 DogLauncher 程序
If we look at it--
看一下...
If we look at our dog launching procedure, it was very simple.
DogLauncher 程序非常简单
We create a dog and have it make noise.
我们创造了一只狗，并让它发出声音
But we could have a more complicated situation.
但有时会遇到更复杂的情况
So here is a little more detailed terminology.
所以需要知道一些更详细的术语
On this first line, we have the declaration of a dog variable.
第一行是 Dog 变量的声明
We say there is a dog variable called smallDog.
有一个叫 smallDog 的变量
But at this point, we haven't actually created any kind of dog at all.
但其实还没有创建出狗
There's been no instantiation.
还没有实例化
There's just a place that a dog could go.
只有一个狗可以呆的地方
This is the opposite.
第二行正相反
This is creating a dog of size 20 but then not putting it anywhere.
这行创造了一只体重为20的狗，却没有把它放在任何地方
And in this case, since nobody uses it,
这种情况下没人使用它
it will just get destroyed by the so-called garbage collector.
它就会被垃圾回收器销毁
Very scary.
非常可怕
But we'll cover that stuff later.
我们以后会讲的
And for now, you can just know that if you instantiate dogs,
现在只需要知道如果实例化狗
they'll be destroyed by some kind of ruthless garbage collector.
只会被某种无情的垃圾回收器毁掉
Now, if you want to avoid losing your dog,
如果你想避免失去狗
you want to put it somewhere.
就要把它放在什么地方
So in this case, this line of code instantiates a dog and then assigns it to an already declared variable.
所以此行代码实例化一条狗，然后将其赋给已经声明的变量
So this is instantiation and assignment.
这就是实例化和赋值
Though often, what you'll do is you'll do all three.
通常这三项都要做
I declare there is a variable named hugeDog.
我声明一个叫 hugeDog 的变量
We instantiate it, and then we assign that new dog to the hugeDog variable.
然后实例化狗，并其赋给 hugeDog 变量
And then here, we have a couple of so-called invocations.
这里有几个引用
So here, I am saying, hugeDog, I would like you to invoke your makeNoise method.
这里是说：“ hugeDog，引用你的 makeNoise 方法”
And this dot you can think of as meaning a member of, right?
这个点可以想象成类的成员
So it belongs to this class.
它属于这个类
And so as far as terminology goes,
所以就术语而言
that's all we need for now.
现在掌握这些就可以了
And we'll move towards looking at a little more in-depth picture of what static means.
稍后会更深入地了解 static 的含义
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
But first, one more thing.
但在那之前还有一件事